A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Shenandoah County (Box 135, Folder 7-17)
      - Supin Lick Mountain: H.V. Butler, 1941 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Hellman, J.H.: 1944 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Rakes, Hugh N.: 1945 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - Wiley, C.W.: 208 acres, 1957 (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1949 (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Southampton County (Box 135, Folder 18-22)
      - Charlie's Hope Plantation: H. Stuart Lewis, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - Franklin Peanut Company: n.d. (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - Raiford, W. Burnley: 223 acres, 1942 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1940 (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 135, Folder 22)
    - Spotsylvania County (Box 136-137)
      - Beachwood Farm: B.S. Dickinson, 1948-1949 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - East View Farm: Tom Woolfolk, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Green Branch: J.L. Hoff, 1942-1950 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Green Gate: W.E. Sherman, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Hickory Point: George C. Rawlings, 1958-1959 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - Holladay Mills: Brian Holladay, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Kenilworth: Otto Williams, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Linden Forest: T.D. Kerns, 1954-1955 (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Linden Hall: 45 acres, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Mannsfield Hall: Mannsfield Hall Country Club, 1931-1937 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - Mill Garden Farm: G.A. Marshall, 1937 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - Nottingham Farm: Willis and Garnett (attorneys), 1956 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      - Pickett Dale Farms: S.H. Saul, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      - Pine Forest: H.E. DeJarnette, 1949-1963 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      - Rockland Farm: W.A.C. Pettit, 1938 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      - Rockland: J.S. Purcell, 1941 (Box 136, Folder 16)
      - Whig Hill: F.W. Sanford, 1936 (Box 136, Folder 17)
      - Whig Hill: M. Wishner, 1960 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      - Colbert, C.W.: 432 acres, 1943 (Box 136, Folder 19)
      - Dillard, W.R.: 312 acres, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 20)
      - Faulconer, G.Z.: 50 acres, 1948 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Samuels, Joseph: 397 acres, 1953 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1952 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Stafford County (Box 137-138)
      - Chapel Green: Charles E. Spencer, 1953-1957 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Chapel Green: William W. Campbell, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Evendale: Helen Hull Jacobs, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Fairholen Dairy Farm: G.M. Harrison, 1941 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Ferry Farm: Mabelle H. Colbert, 1942-1943 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Grafton Hall: C.F. Blackburn, 1936 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Green Bank Farm: A.W. Kay, 1943-1954 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - Greenway: Fred B. Hoyt, 1930's (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - Hartwood Manor: Frank S. Flynn, 1958 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - Journey End: Salkeld Stamper, 1949 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - Little Falls Farm: R.M. Brewer, 1942 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - Lovers Leap: J.H. Helman, 1953 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - Wake Robin: Ira L. Kimes, 1936-1937 (Box 137, Folder 17)
      - Woodlawn: J. Brabner-Smith, 1930's (Box 137, Folder 18)
      - Ashby, James: 400 acres, 1942 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Brown, Elizabeth H.: 6 acres, 1948 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Clift, S.P.: 244 acres, 1939 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Garofalo, Marie: 91 acres, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Russell, Arthur O.: 5 acres, 1955 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1940 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Surry County (Box 138-140)
      - Aspen Grove: W.E. Barnes, 1942 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Claremont Manor: Millicent A. Rogers, 1948-1950 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Claremont School: William E. Crawford, 1928 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Cross Creek Hunting Club: A.B. Gill, 1932 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Eastover: Albert H. Ochsner, 1936-1956 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - Flying Point: James River Lumber Company, 1954 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      - Flying Point Farm: 275 acres, 1951 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - Four Mile Tree: R.P. Rawls, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - Glebe House: E.M. Bryant, 1964 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - Hog Island: J.A. Bozarth, 1932-1947 (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - Longview-on-James: Joseph Reed Routten, 1937-1946 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Montpelier: C.B. Faison, 1956, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Mount Pleasant: Franz Von Schilling, 1956 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Oak Hill: B.W. Perkins, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Oak Hill: Gordon C. Berryman, 1950 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Pipsco: Henry L. Jones, 1934-1939 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Pleasant Point: Willis Morrison, 1935-1949 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Pleasant Point: R.C. Beuchoten, 1953 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Pleasant Point: Ernest W. Goodrich, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Quicohanna: Ashley P. Cutchin, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Quicohanna: Ashley P. Cutchin, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Swann's Point: Garland Gray, 1931-1953 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Woodgreen: 80 acres, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Belding, O.D.: 25 acres, 1940 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Forney, H.B.: 35 acres, 1955 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Hopper, J. Lewis: 30-35 acres, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Hopper, James: 53 acres, 1954 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - James River Lumber Company: 3649 acres, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Jones, Walter: 465 acres, 1940-1941, 1950 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Lawrence, Thomas: 100 acres, 1950 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Mills, L.L.: 2 acres, 1951 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1935-1940 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Sussex County (Box 140, Folder 11-13)
      - Montrose: Robert H. Stephenson, 1964 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Oakland: Lucy M. Raines, 1961 (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Tazewell County (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - Haw Ridge: Anne Brooke Gibson (agent), n.d. (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Warren County (Box 140, Folder 15-23)
      - Aspen Grove: M.O. Simpson, 1947-1950 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - Killahevlin: W.H. Lipscomb, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Liberty Hall: Frank Gibb, 1949 (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - Liberty Hall: Clyde Columbia, 1954 (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - Skyline Caverns: H.B. Long, 1951-1953 (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - Spangler Hall: 1972 (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - Ross, Eva B.: 218 acres, 1947 (Box 140, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1975 (Box 140, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Warwick County (Box 140-141)
      - Balthorp Farm: H.G. Moyer, 1934 (Box 140, Folder 24)
      - Hilton Village Colony Inn: W.E. Smyre, 1946 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Lee Hall Estate: W.G. Stone, 1938-1940 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1937, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Westmoreland County (Box 141-145)
      - Albany: Mr. Osbelt, 1937 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Aqua Duck: V.A. Folden, 1957-1959 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Arlington Farm: John P. Cooke, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Beales Mill: R.H. Beale, 1937 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Beales Mill Pond: 1958 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Bleak Hall: William C. Nalle, 1937-1940 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Bleak Hall: Willie Dodd, 1941 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Bluff Point: Mr. Ware, 1960 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - Bushfield: Mark S. Willing, 1940-1944 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Bushfield: Archer St. John, 1955-1960 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Cary's Corner: E.C. Griffeth, 1942-1943 (Box 141, Folder 14)
      - Claymont: Richard Washington, 1940 (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - Claymount: Gillette Conner, 1962 (Box 141, Folder 16)
      - Drum Bay Farm: E.B. Hutt, 1937, 1943 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - Emily's Beach Haven: James J. Charters, 1961-1962 (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - The Glebe: Irwin H. Linton, 1934-1942 (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - The Glebe: Irwin H. Linton, 1963 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      - The Glebe: photographs (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Heronwood: John Walsh, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Kinsale: n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Liberty: Julian H. Griffeth, 1941-1958 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Monrovia: Evert J. Deneve, 1943-1944 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Montross: Gabriel Elias, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Mount Pleasant: D.L. Thornberry, 1932-1937 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Mount Pleasant: James L. King, 1961 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - The Oaks: H.S. Marmaduke, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Old Colony Inn: Lee A. Williams, 1947 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Panorama: H.E. Smith, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Pomona: F.C. Haislip, 1955 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Riverfield Farm: F. Dew Claybrook, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Roxbury: Lesbia S. Alexander, 1937 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - Royal Oak: E.L. Courtney, 1940 (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - Sandy Point: 150 acres, 1930's (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Tidwells: Kathleen Ficklin, 1937-1947 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - Twiford: H.W. Coates, 1937-1941 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - Twiford: J.E. Gouldman, 1958 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - Walnut Hill Farm: Sue Eaton West, 1952 (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - Wilton: Arthur W. Roberts, 1954-1962 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Wilton: LeGrand Real Estate Agency, pre-1957 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Wirtland: Burton H. Slocum, 1957 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Balderson, Calvin M.: 25 acres, 1958 (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Balderson, Calvin M.: 4 1/2 and 25 acres, 1958 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Braun, M.E.: 6 acres, 1961 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Bronson, Howard C.: 10 acres, 1950-1951 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Bucy, Edmund H.: 7 acres, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Bullis, Harry: 8 acres, 1956 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Coggin, R. Marshall: 4 1/2 acres, 1948-1949 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Drucker, S.: 250 acres, 1944-1945 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Fisher, David Richard: 1962, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Gibbs, Charles L.: 4 1/2 acres, 1960-1964 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Haislip, F.C.: 11 acres, 1959-1960 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Hall, Sam: 1945 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Harvey, J.W.: 520 acres, 1937 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Hawkins, A.J.: 1961 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Holm, Carl: 14 acres, 1957 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Horton, R.G.: 1949 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Hutt, E.B.: 150 acres, 1944-1947 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Jennings, G.A.C.: 1960 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Jones, F.S.: 240 acres, 1943 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Jones, W.L.: 1 acre, 1961 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Martin, Mr.: 1971 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Moon, Luther: 42 acres, 1942 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Newton, Edward C.: 20 acres, 1956 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Oden, Mr.: 400 acres, 1964 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - Potomac Supply Company: 21 acres, 1951 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - Potomac Supply Company: 1958-1965 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - Rice, Mr.: 57 acres, 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Schacht, William: 1958 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - Schlegel, Roy D.: 1957 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Taylor, S.H.: 277 acres, 1945-1950 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Trader, Le Merle: 1 acre, 1960 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Truett, J.E.: 283 acres, 1960 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Truett, J.E.: 1968 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - Walker, J.D.: 32 acres, 1961 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Watson, D.H.: 7 1/2 acres, 1962 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Weible, John R.: 1959-1960 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Wilson, George: 4 acres, 1956 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Woodall, Seth S.: 2 acres, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1957 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1940-1941, 1952, 1974 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Williamsburg (Box 145, Folder 9-18)
      - Bull, William J.: 1966 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Cosby, R.W.: 1955 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Craighill, Mary W.: 1949 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Dear, Elizabeth: 1954-1955 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Peyton, Thomas G.: 1955 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Rome, Sydney: 1953 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Weaver, W.S.: 1955-1956 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - Woody, May P.: 1952 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1949, 1955 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Wise County (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - York County (Box 146)
      - Bigler's Farm: E.W. Maynard, 1938 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Famsed Point: Florence A. Monfalcone, 1967 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Gibson Farm: Charles T. Gibson, 1936 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Marlbank: Mr. Mulcahy, 1930-1940 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Mouquin: Henry F. Mouquin, 1933-1935 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Porte Bello: Richard W. Mahone, 1934 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Post Farm: W.S. Ewan, 1934-1936 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Ripon Hall: R.D. Calkins, 1936-1941 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Waterview: Fred Hodges, 1944-1949 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Anderson, W.J.: 1934 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Bowers, Mrs.: 1940 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Holland, W.J.: 1954 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Hopkins, C.W.: 8 acres, 1933 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - Jacob, C.C.: 1949 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Jones, Ben: 37 acres, 1956 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Lackey, M.O.: 1946 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - O'Hara, Mrs.: 15 acres, 1947 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Worrom, J.S.: 22 acres, 1949 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1934, 1954 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1937 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 146, Folder 21)
  - Out-of-state real estate (Box 147-149)
    - Alabama (Box 147, Folder 1-2)
      - Vredenburgh Saw Mill Company (Vredenburgh): 1946-1949 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: n.d. (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Eastern Military Academy (Stamford): Consolidated Equipment Company, 1949 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Delaware (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Florida (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Maine (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Maryland (Box 147-148)
      - Bulle Rock Farm (Centreville): R.J. Funkhauser, 1955 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Chester House (Centreville): Eastern Shore Estates Company, 1971 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Kingston Hall (Somerset County): J.H. Lee Fisher, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Liberty Hall (Somerset County): John A. Christoffel, 1956 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - Mount Republican (Charles County): 400 acres, 1936-1959 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - Mount Republican (Charles County): photographs (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - Rose Hill Farm: Russell Eldridge, 1961-1964 (Box 147, Folder 13)
      - Green, Sydney (Dorchester County): 110 acres, 1950 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - Wilson, Oscar E. (Princess Anne County): 1950 (Box 147, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1934, 1945-1947, 1951, 1955, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina (Box 148-149)
      - Belhaven Lumber Industries (Belhaven): G. Hodges Bryant, 1953-1956 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Belvidere Plantation (Perquimas County): Jack M. Winslow, 1961 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Beverly Hall (Edenton): Richard D. Dixon, 1946 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Davis Island (Carteret County): Edward S. Carnell, 1935 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Edgewater Club (Carteret County): Edgewater Club, 1934 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Edgewater Club-Hotel (Carteret County): F.M. Simmons, 1939 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Fort Caswell Harbor (Southport): 1933 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Hog Island (Craven County): A.W. Nelson, 1931-1937 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Hotel Concord (Concord): Ralph H. Bevier, 1950 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Hotel John Hewes (Edenton): L.A. Perry, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - Penny Hill Club (Corolla): Lloyd O'Neal, 1938 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - Sleepy Point (Gloucester): C.R. Davant, 1940 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - Smith Island (Brunswick County): T.L. Boyd, 1933-1934 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - Bryant, G. Hodges (Belhaven): 1956 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - Foushee, W.H. (Wake Forest): 14 acres, 1947 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - Gary, H.H. (Knotts Island): 500 acres, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1939, 1947-1963 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - South Carolina (Box 149, Folder 4-8)
      - Long Island (Charleston County): John Gracy, 1945-1947 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Oaks Plantation (Goose Creek): H.W. Conant, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Orange Grove (Beaufort County): John B. Snow, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1948 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee (Box 149, Folder 9-11)
      - Dodge-Plymouth dealership (Johnson City): T.E. Deakins, 1953 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1953 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Texas (Box 149, Folder 12)
      - Rinehart, John R. (New Braunfels): 1965 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - West Virginia (Box 149, Folder 13-16)
      - Cedar Lawn (Jefferson County): 1955 (Box 149, Folder 13)
      - Claymont (Charles Town): Robert H. Fletcher, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 14)
      - Fairfield (Monroe County): Mr. Moody, 1953 (Box 149, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 149, Folder 16)
- Oversize
  Arranged into Virginia real estate maps and plats (Sub-series A), out-of-state real estate maps and plats (Sub-series B), and miscellaneous and unidentified real estate maps and plats (Sub-series C). Sub-series A and Sub-series B principally contain larger items that were removed from Series I, Sub-series A and Sub-series B. Oversized items with corresponding files in Series I have been noted within each folder and catalogued in this aid under identical headings. Consequently, this series' sub-series are arranged congruently with Series I.
  Sub-series A and B mainly contain maps and blueprints depicting plats purchased, bought, and sold by George B. Lorraine. Of note are United States geological and topographical survey maps and Virginia primary and secondary highway maps denoting locations of properties, survey maps, and blueprints depicting architectural features, crop placement, and landscape features. While maps and plats comprise the bulk of these sub-series, other oversize material may be included in each folder. This smaller amount of material includes advertisements, deeds, floor plans, and aerial photographs.
  Sub-series C is unidentified real estate maps and plats and miscellaneous oversize material consisting of United States Army Corps of Engineers geological survey maps, Virginia highway maps, tourist road maps, a genealogical chart for the Fitzhugh-Grymes family of King George County, Virginia, a Stan Fenelle drawing of Secretariat, and a Louisa County Soil Survey. United States Army Corps of Engineers maps and Virginia highway maps may contain property locations and descriptions of unidentified properties.
  - Virginia real estate maps and plats
    - Accomack County
      - Michael Marsh: 1955 (folder 1)
    - Albemarle County
      - Craigmillar: James B. Gilmer, 1931 (folder 1)
      - East Belmont: Mrs. Harrison Taylor and H.C. Huffer, 1938-1947 (folder 2)
      - Ednam: Marjorie Copps, 1937 (folder 3)
      - Guthrie Hall: Louise Jenkins Kinney, 1936-1939 (folder 4)
      - Keswick: Thomas Walker Page, 1936 (folder 5)
      - Lone Oak Farm: T.N. Steinbland, 1962 (folder 6)
      - Pantops Farm: William R. Stevens, 1948-1949 (folder 7)
      - Piedmont Manor: Howard Friend, 1934-1952 (folder 8)
      - Viewmont: Joshua Fry, et. al., 1934 (folder 8a)
    - Amelia County
      - Wigwam: 1929 (folder 9)
      - Woodland: H.M. Williams, 1937-1944 (folder 10)
    - Arlington
      - Rixey, John: 120 acres, 1938-1939 (folder 11)
    - Augusta County
      - Swannanoa: Swannanoa Development Corporation, 1927-1944 (folder 12)
      - Swannanoa: Swannanoa Development Corporation, 1939-1944 (folder 13)
    - Bath County
      - Wavecrest: 1350 acres, n.d. (folder 14)
    - Brunswick County
      - Brunswick Plantation: R.A. Harris, 1956 (folder 15)
    - Buckingham County
      - Dungannon: Kale L. Bruno, 1936-1940 (folder 16)
      - Mount Ida: Joint Stock Land Bank, 1932-1934 (folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous letter file (folder 18)
    - Caroline County
      - Blenheim: Retta G.H. Lowry, 1936-1946 (folder 19)
      - Chestnut Valley: R.E. Bell, 1936-1960 (folder 20)
      - North Wales: J. Louis Reynolds, 1941-1953 (folder 21)
      - Rock Stop Farm: Helen Hull Jacobs, 1937-1948, 1960 (folder 22)
      - Singing River Plantation: Mrs. Curtis Drake Cecil, 1953 (folder 23)
      - Thornberry Farm: H.H. George, Jr., 1952 (folder 24)
      - Fennel, William: n.d. (folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous letter file (folder 26)
    - Charles City County
      - Greenway, 1934 (folder 26a)
      - Riverwood: Lucia Martin, 1960 (folder 27)
      - Hill, Edward: 1962 (folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (folder 29)
    - Charlotte County
      - Gravel Hill: Rufus C. Phillips, Jr., 1967 (folder 30)
      - Roanoke Plantation: 1953 (folder 31)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (folder 32)
    - Chesterfield County
      - Physic Hill: Frank Robius, 1954 (folder 33)
      - Bellwood, E.C.: 800 acres, 1941 (folder 34)
      - Gilliam, J.P.: 1925 (folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous letter file (folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (folder 3)
    - Culpeper County
      - Quiet Shade: John M. Garret, 1938-1943 (folder 36)
    - Cumberland County
      - Clifton: Wistar Anderson, 1935 (folder 37)
      - Clifton: Robert Toomay, Jr., 1969 (folder 38)
      - Trice Lake: A.B. Hardee, 1956 (folder 39)
    - Dinwiddie County
      - Whippernock: M.D. Goodrich, 1952-1954 (folder 1)
    - Elizabeth City County
      - Grand View: L.R. Carson, 1934-1936 (folder 2)
    - Essex County
      - Mount Clement: Clagett H. Pattie, 1940-1948 (folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (folder 4)
    - Fairfax County
      - Turner, Scott: 243 acres, 1942 (folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estates listings (folder 6)
    - Fauquier County
      - Delaplane: C.L. Delaplane, 1936-1939 (folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous letter file (folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County
      - Carysbrook: J.W. Holland, 1960 (folder 9)
      - Wilmington: Floyd H. Fry, 1960 (folder 10)
    - Gloucester County
      - Glen Roy: Casey Realty Company, 1961 (folder 11)
      - Kempville: G.N. Armstrong, 1938-1945 (folder 12)
      - Lands End: Wyatt Carneal, 1942-1946 (folder 13)
      - Old Purton: Thomas P. Duncan, 1956 (folder 14)
      - Rivermere: Earl Fisher, 1959-1967 (folder 15)
      - Severnby: Katherine P. Withers, 1956 (folder 16)
      - Summerville: Mary Lee Tabb, 1953-1954 (folder 17)